Guide to the Alfred A. Hart Photographs PC0002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Prints, Series 1
  - Photograph album
    - Pleasant Valley, looking West, Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 301 (Box 1)
      Pleasant Valley; Truckee River; Canyon; telegraph pole
      G-306
    - Pleasant Valley, looking East, Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 302 (Box 1)
      Pleasant Valley; Truckee River; telegraph pole
      G-307
      80
    - Red Bluffs, looking from the West. Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 303 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Red Bluffs; Canyon; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon); telegraph pole
      G-308
    - Looking West from Red Bluffs, Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 304 (Box 1)
      Red Bluffs; Truckee River; Canyon; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon); telegraph pole
      G-309
    - Red Bluffs, Lower Canyon of Truckee, 178 miles from Sacramento., 305 (Box 1)
      Red Bluffs; Truckee River; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon); telegraph pole
      G-310
    - Construction Train on Desert, near Humboldt Lake., 310 (Box 1)
      Desert; Train; Boxcar
      G-311
      Humbolt River, The Desert
      81
    - Construction Train on Alkali Dessert [sic]., 311 (Box 1)
      Train; Desert; Boxcar
      G-312
      Humboldt River, The Desert
    - Alkali Flat. Construction train in distance., 312 (Box 1)
      G-313
    - Chinese Camp, Brown’s Station., 313 (Box 1)
      Chinese; Desert; telegraph pole
      G-314
    - Brown’s Station, 234 miles from Sacramento., 314 (Box 1)
      Brown’s Station; Boxcar; telegraph pole
      G-315
      82
    - Water Train, opposite Humboldt Lake., 315 (Box 1)
      Water train; Humboldt Lake; Desert; telegraph pole
      G-316
    - End of Track, near Humboldt Lake., 316 (Box 1)
      Wagons; Desert; Teamsters; Camp; telegraph pole
      G-317
    - End of Track, on Humboldt Plains., 317 (Box 1)
      Desert; Laborers; Chinese; telegraph pole
      G-318
    - Lower Crossing Humboldt River, 254 miles from Sacramento., 318 (Box 1)
      Water tank; telegraph pole
      G-319
      83
    - Winnemucca Depot, 334 miles from Sacramento., 319 (Box 1)
      Winnemucca, Nevada; Water train; Depot; Locomotive
      G-320
    - Winnemucca Town and Peak. 334 miles from Sacramento., 320 (Box 1)
      Winnemucca, Nevada; Winnemucca Peak
      G-321
    - Advance of Civilization. End of Track near Iron Point., 321 (Box 1)
      Iron Point
      G-322
      yes
    - Advance of Civilization. Scene on the Humboldt Desert., 322 (Box 1)
      Boxcar; Laborers; Wagons; Humboldt Desert; telegraph pole
      G-323
      84
    - Shoshone Indians looking at Locomotive on Desert., 323 (Box 1)
      Shoshone Indians; Locomotive; Water train
      G-324
    - Shoshone Indians, Humboldt Plains., 324 (Box 1)
      Shoshone Indians; Desert; Humboldt Plains
      G-325
    - Car of Sup’t of Construction. End of Track., 325 (Box 1)
      Strobridge family
      G-326
    - Argenta Station, at Skull Ranch, 395 miles from Sacramento., 326 (Box 1)
      Argenta Station; Skull Ranch; Desert; telegraph pole
      G-327
      85
    - Chinese Camp, at End of Track., 327 (Box 1)
      Chinese Camp; Boxcar; Train; telegraph pole
      G-328
    - Powder Bluff, West end of 10 mile Canyon., 328 (Box 1)
      Powder Bluff; Locomotive; Ten Mile Canyon; Laborers; telegraph pole
      G-329
    - Second Crossing of Humboldt River. 430 miles from Sacramento., 329 (Box 1)
      Boxcar; Desert; Laborers
      G-330
    - Commencement of a Snow Storm. Scene East of Second Crossing of Humboldt., 330 (Box 1)
      Train; Boxcar; Flatcar; telegraph pole
      G-331
      86
    - Sentinel Rock, Ten Mile Canyon., 331 (Box 1)
      Sentinel Rock; Ten Mile Canyon; Humboldt River; Boxcar; telegraph pole
      G-332
    - Team Camp--Evening View, End of Track., 332 (Box 1)
      Boxcar
      G-333
    - Curving Iron, Ten Mile Canyon., 333 (Box 1)
      Laborers; Ten Mile Canyon; Humboldt River; telegraph pole
      G-334
      Humboldt River, TheDesert
    - Humboldt Gate, Ten Mile Canyon., 334 (Box 1)
      Humboldt Gate; Ten Mile Canyon; Humboldt River; telegraph pole
      G-335
      87
    - Building Water Tank. Trout Creek Mountains in distance., 335 (Box 1)
      Trout Creek Mountains; Laborers
      G-336
    - Entering the Palisades, Ten Mile Canyon., 336 (Box 1)
      Palisades; Humboldt River; Ten Mile Canyon; Train; telegraph pole
      G-338
    - The Palisades--Ten Mile Canyon. 435 miles from Sacramento., 337 (Box 1)
      Palisades; Ten Mile Canyon; Boxcar; Humboldt River
      G-337
    - First Construction Train passing the Palisades, Ten Mile Canyon., 338 (Box 1)
      Train; Ten Mile Canyon; Palisades; Laborers
      G-339
      88
    - Alcove in Palisades, Ten Mile Canyon., 339 (Box 1)
      Palisades; Ten Mile Canyon; Train; telegraph pole
      G-340
    - Indian Viewing R.R. from top of Palisades. 435 miles from Sacramento., 340 (Box 1)
      Indian; Humboldt River; Palisades; Canyon
      G-341
    - View across River and Canyon, from top of Palisades., 341 (Box 1)
      Canyon; Humboldt River; Palisades
      G-342
    - Shoshone Indians, Ten Mile Canyon., 342 (Box 1)
      Shoshone Indians; Ten Mile Canyon; Humboldt River
      G-343
      89
    - Train at Argenta. 396 miles from Sacramento., 343 (Box 1)
      Argenta, Nevada; Locomotive; Boxcar; telegraph pole
      G-344
    - Machine Shops at Carlin. 445 miles from Sacramento., 344 (Box 1)
      Carlin, Nevada; Locomotive; telegraph pole
      G-345
    - Carlin from the Water Tanks, Looking West., 345 (Box 1)
      Carlin, Nevada; Boxcar
      G-346
    - Depot at Elko. 468 miles from Sacramento., 346 (Box 1)
      Elko, Nevada; Depot; telegraph pole
      G-347
      90
    - Elko from the West. 468 miles from Sacramento., 347 (Box 1)
      Elko, Nevada; Camp; telegraph pole
      G-348
    - Water Tank at Peko. 488 miles from Sacramento., 348 (Box 1)
      Water tank; Peko, Nevada; Train; telegraph pole
      G-349
    - Scene near Deeth. Mount Halleck in distance., 349 (Box 1)
      Deeth, Nevada; Mount Halleck; Train; telegraph pole
      G-350
    - Railroad Camp near Victory. 10 1/4 miles laid in one day., 350 (Box 1)
      Camp; Boxcar; Laborers; Flatcar; telegraph pole
      G-351
      Wahsatch Range, Great Salt Lake
      91
    - Monument Point from the Lake. 669 miles from Sacramento., 351 (Box 1)
      Monument Point; Train; Locomotive; Combine car; Boxcar; Flatcar; Jupiter
      G-352
    - Salt Lake from Monument Point. 669 miles from Sacramento., 352 (Box 1)
      Great Salt Lake; Train; Locomotive; telegraph pole; Flatcar; Combine car; Laborers; Jupiter
      G-353
    - Poetry and Prose. Scene at Monument Point, North end of Salt Lake., 353 (Box 1)
      Great Salt Lake; Train; Wagon train; telegraph pole; Locomotive; Jupiter
      G-354
    - First Greeting of the Iron Horse. Promontory Point, May 9th, 1869., 354 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Promontory, Utah; telegraph pole; Laborers; Jupiter
      G-355
      92
    - Last Rail--The Invocation. Fixing the wire, May 10, 1869., 355 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Laborers; telegraph pole; Promontory, Utah; Jupiter
      G-356
    - Last Rail is Laid. Scene at Promontory Point, May 10, 1869., 356 (Box 1)
      Promontory, Utah; telegraph pole; Stanford, Leland; Strobridge, J.H.; Durant, T.C.; Duff, John; Dillon, Sidney; Strobridge, Mrs.; Ryan, Mrs.
      G-357
    - Rival Monarchs. Scene at Promontory Point, May 10, 1869., 357 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; telegraph pole; Promontory, Utah; No. 119
      G-358
    - Monarch from the West. Scene at Promontory Point, May 10, 1869., 358 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; telegraph pole; Promontory, Utah; Jupiter
      G-359
      93
    - Monarch from the East. Scene at Promontory Point, May 10, 1869., 359 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Promontory, Utah; No. 119
      G-360
    - Last Act--690 miles from Sacramento. Scene at Promontory Point, May 10, 1869., 360 (Box 1)
      Promontory, Utah; Train; telegraph pole
      G-361
    - Looking West from Taylor’s Mills. Near Ogden., 361 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Taylor’s Mills; Laborers; No. 119
      G-362
    - Taylor’s Mills, Wahsatch Range. Near Ogden., 362 (Box 1)
      Taylor’s Mills, Utah; Wasatch Mountains
      G-363
      94
    - Ogden and Wahsatch Range. 742 miles from Sacramento., 363 (Box 1)
      Ogden, Utah; Wasatch Mountains; Great Salt Lake
      G-364
    - Railroad at Ogden, Wahsatch Range in distance., 364 (Box 1)
      Stanford, Leland; Wasatch Mountains; Locomotivie; Caboose; No. 117
      G-365
    - Donner Lake, from Railroad, around Crested Peak., 501 (Box 1)
      G-250
      64
    - Castle Peak and Donner Lake. View from Railroad., 502 (Box 1)
      Castle Peak; Donner Lake
      G-252
    - Mirror Cove and Crested Peak, Donner Lake., 504 (Box 1)
      Mirror Cove; Crested Peak; Donner Lake
      G-254
      65
    - Railroad and Pass over Western Summit, from foot of Donner Lake., 505 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Girl
      G-251
    - Railroad around Donner Lake, from foot of lake., 506 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Boating Party; Strobridge Family
      G-253
    - Snow at Cisco, in the month of May., 608 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California
      G-191
    - Fourth Crossing of Truckee River, Eastern Summit of Sierras in distance., 706 (Box 1)
      G-286
    - Levee at Sacramento, looking north from steamer., 832 (Box 1)
      Sacramento River; Boxcar
      G-2
  - Album pages (Box 6)
  - Copy prints (Box 7)
  - Copy slides made from album images (Box 8)
- Stereographs, Series 2
  - #1-29 (Box 1)
  - #30-90 (Box 2)
  - #93-125 (Box 3)
  - #126-494 (Box 4)
  - Stanford residence, Sacramento (Box 5)
  - Duplicates (Box 9)
- Additional Stereographs, Accession ARCH-1996-141
  - Stereographs No. 65, 71, and 81 (Box 1)
- Duplicate stereographs, Accession ARCH-2000-339 (Box 1)